

K' Long

C# .NET DEVELOPER

SKILLS

FRONT-END

- HTML, CSS: JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP
- ANGULARJS

BACK-END

- C# .NET MVC
- WEB API

OTHER

- GIT
- RESTFUL API
- AZURE

CERTIFICATES

TOEIC

SCORE: 675 08/2022

Listening & Reading

INTERESTS

MUSIC PROGRAMMING

MIDI

READING

GAME

TECHNOLOGY

8 About me

I am majoring in software engineering.

I'm familiar with C#, ASP.NET MVC,.NET WEB API, Java, and Android. I am also interested in MIDI and music programming.

Currently, I am focusing on web development with ASP.NET and ASP.NET Core. and I also have some experience working with this framework.

My goal in the next 3 years is to become a software developer specializing in the.NET and.NET CORE frameworks.

10/10/1999

klong101099@gmail.com

P Ho Chi Minh City

10/10/1999

Ho Chi Minh City

10/10/1999

Ho Chi Minh City

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

10/10/1999

f https://www.facebook.com/longkelvin101099

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/long-kelvin-196a87181/

S live:.cid.a2e714512da2b6f4 https://longkelvin.github.io/

WORK EXPERIENCES

.NET DEVELOPER

8/2021 - 12/2021

ELCA VN

Main Responsibilities:

- Learn process (C# WPF, .NET Core, NHibernate, Bitbucket, XAML, NUnitTest)
- Code and implement both the API and User Interface for WPF project.



.NET DEVELOPER

1/1/2021 - 30/6/2021

VIHAT TECHNOLOGY CO

Main Responsibilities:

- Learn process (C#.NET MVC, Entity framework, Git, Agile)
- Mantain and implement new features for SMS and OTP web app.
- Design SQL Database for web app.

EDUCATION



SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2017 - 2022

VNUHCM - UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

PERSONAL PROJECTS

COFFEESHOP_NETMVC

1/3/2022 - 1/8/2022

- https://github.com/LongKelvin/CoffeeShopNetMVC
- C# .NET MVC, ANGULARJS
- CoffeeShop is a personal project I created with the aim of applying the knowledge I have learned to create a website for small and medium-sized coffee shops.
- Coffeeshop is made to perform the duties of an e-commerce website, such as managing products, placing orders, and accepting payments online through services like MoMo and Internet banking.

EZMIDI PIANO

1/9/2020 - 30/7/2021

- https://github.com/LongKelvin/EzMidiPiano
- JAVA ANDROID, C++ JNI
- EzMidiPiano is an Android app provides a Midi connection and javax.sound.midi for the Android phone.
- EzMidiPiano allows the use of a MIDI controller device to play synthesizer sounds.
- It contains many instruments for playing and testing midi devices, as well as the ability to bind Midi data to the keyboard.

ASSET MANAGEMENT

2019 - 2020

- C# .NET CORE, ANGULAR 8
- https://github.com/LongKelvin/ASPNET_CORE_QLST
- Asset management for business

MINI SHOP MANAGEMENT APPLICATION

2019 - 2019

- C# WINFORM, SQL SERVER
- https://github.com/LongKelvin/QLST-1
- A small managerment app in C# Winform